SPEAKER 1: Hello everyone.
Bill Luan: 大家好
SPEAKER 2: Hi.
Tenghui Zhu: 你好
SPEAKER 3: Today's episode is all about good times.
Wesley Chun: 今天的节目都是关于美好时光的
SPEAKER 4: First thing, you need a Google account.
Lisa Wray: 首先，你需要有 Google 帐户
If you don't have one, that's easy to fix.
如果你还没有 那很容易
SPEAKER 5: Doing so will reward you
Colt McAnlis: 这样做，你得到的奖励是
with a plethora of colors and bars on your device.
你的设备上会多出 很多色彩和条纹
SPEAKER 3: Engaging users in an immersive, enjoyable
Wesley Chun: 通过身临其境 充满乐趣的体验来
experience.
吸引用户
SPEAKER 2: To help you make your graphics look their best.
Tenghui Zhu: 为了让你的图形 达到最佳效果
SPEAKER 6: That kind of intelligence
Mani Doraisamy: 那种智能
will be built inside the software.
将创建在软件内部
SPEAKER 7: Our team here at Google
Tim Anderson: 我们在谷歌这里的团队
works closely with app developers.
与应用开发者 紧密合作
SPEAKER 8: What kind of challenges
Laurence Moroney: 什么样的挑战
do you see developers facing and what are we
是开发者所面临的 什么是我们
doing to make their lives easier?
正在做的 为了使他们的生活更轻松
SPEAKER 9: Great apps engage all learners.
Jennifer Pahlka: 了不起的应用 会吸引使所有的学习者
And so we did a very simple web app that
我们做了一个非常简单的 Web应用
lets you type in your address and the age of your kid,
你可以输入地址和 孩子的年龄
and it would tell you which schools
它会告诉你 哪个学校
you were eligible to attend.
你有资格入学
SPEAKER 10: So you can think of today's episode
Todd Kerpelman: 你可以把今天的节目看作
as a little bit of extra credit.
额外的一点点积分
SPEAKER 2: So how does this help you?
Tenghui Zhu: 这如何帮助你呢？
SPEAKER 4: Let's take a look.
Lisa Wray: 让我们来看看
SPEAKER 3: Look.
SPEAKER 3：你看
That dinner reservation is on my Google calendar
Google 日历上 有我预订的晚餐
so I don't forget.
我不会忘记
SPEAKER 11: These are things that you can worry less about.
Francis Ma: 这些事不会再占用你的精力
SPEAKER 9: But with a fundamental understanding
Jennifer Pahlka: 有了基本的
of how the digital world works.
对数字世界如何工作的 理解
SPEAKER 3: Highlighting what matters most to users.
Wesley Chun: 突出对用户最重要的
SPEAKER 10: But I want to show you something here.
Todd Kerpelman: 我想给你看点东西
SPEAKER 4: What if I told you I was
Lisa Wray: 要是我告诉你
going to do it without using a database or a back-end server?
我不打算用数据库和后台服务器 那会怎样？
SPEAKER 8: Sounds like a lot of fun.
Laurence Moroney: 听起来很有意思
SPEAKER 10: Whoa.
Todd Kerpelman: 哇 （快躲开，有东西掉下来）
SPEAKER 5: This is the type of technical minutia
Colt McAnlis: 此类技术细节
that's worth knowing.
是值得了解的
SPEAKER 9: They've never before realized
Jennifer Pahlka: 他们以前 从来没有意识到
how important geeks are.
极客们是 多么的重要
SPEAKER 8: One billion active.
Laurence Moroney: 十亿活跃的
SPEAKER 11: Yes.
Francis Ma: 是的
SPEAKER 9: And you'll end up with a community of people
Jennifer Pahlka: 最后， 你融入到这样的一个社区
that you really enjoy and feeling really
这里的人让你真的很喜欢 感觉真的很好
good about the work that you guys can do together.
经历了你们可以 一起做的事情
SPEAKER 3: Well, these are just some ideas
Wesley Chun: 这些只是一部分想法
of how to take good experiences and making them great.
如何把好的实践 发扬光大
SPEAKER 4: So now we're done.
Lisa Wray: 到此 我们大功告成
SPEAKER 5: Don't forget to join our Google+ community as well.
Colt McAnlis: 别忘了 还要加入我们的 Google+ 社区
SPEAKER 6: And make software more intelligent.
Mani Doraisamy: 使软件更加智能
SPEAKER 3: And Google takes care of the rest.
Wesley Chun: 让 Google 照顾剩下的
SPEAKER 4: Thanks for watching.
Lisa Wray: 感谢收看
SPEAKER 3: Hope we get an opportunity to serve you again.
Wesley Chun: 希望我们能有机会 再次为您服务